Ahmed Saber

42 Abu wafia off Ahmed Helmy st., shobra masr 11241 Cairo – Egypt – 0101 555 2992 ahmedsaber111@gmail.com

Objective

My background includes 7 years of web designs within the graphic design industry. I have the passion for make creative designs & produce the latest technology in the field of the web design.

Most recently, my experience has been in the CSS 2 table-less complex design, PHP & MYSQL Dreamweaver application developer, SEO search engine optimization. I'm confident that my experience would be an asset to work I provide.

About +40 web design projects achieved & un-estimated prints, logos & graphic design projects.

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER/ DEVELOPER - HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY

Experience

WEB DESIGNER

ECC SOLUTIONS, Cairo March 2011 – Present

Designing and implementing high standard Websites, Web applications and Mobile sites according to the preset requirements.

Handle design issues and daily tasks issued on the ticketing system by different users.

Making sure the client's needs are being met and the creative goals are on track

Creating visually appealing and highly usable UI designs

Building and testing prototypes of your work in an agile environment using the latest technology

Interaction design, information architecture, usability and analysis

WEB DESIGNER/ PHP WEB DEVELOPER

GRAT, CAIRO

October 2009 - March 2011

Design and implement user-driven templates, databases and interfaces for ease of use.

MOODLE administrator, over 21 online exam attended by +160 synchronous students

ERP IMPLEMENTER

ENCOM SOFT, CAIRO

September 2008 - August 2009

Implement ERP client needs From A to Z, initializing ORACLE database on the server & connecting to it the other pc. Imp & Exp dump files, create public synonym and compile views, tables, forms & reports.

Solve client accounting problems.

Handling & execute setup all forms & reports that created & developed via ORACLE developer specially to the client.

WEB DESIGNER/ PHP WEB DEVELOPER

I.I.T.C, CAIRO

May 2008 - February 2009

Implement client needs are the main job priority.

Work & life under pressure of work, up to +5 projects and many tasks have to done in the same time.

PHP & MYSQL Dreamweaver application developer, CSS 2 & SEO search engine optimization is my job description besides graphic designs with Photoshop CS 3 & swish max.

Design web sites belong to web 2 & include it to all available web search engines.

Multi browsers compatibility is the common mistakes that faced me while working, that acquire me the necessary experience to avoid it later.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC/ WEB DESIGNER

AUC, CAIRO

March 2007 - September 2008

"The Right Road" club website.

"Remember the days" Spring 07 graduated book.

Lacoste pack.

Events logos: OSCAR'S NIGHT logo

Education B.S. in Accounting

AIN SHAMS UNIVERSITY, CAIRO

2009

Interests INSPIRATION, KNOWLEDGE

References References are available on request.